komparify.com 2016-12-30

# Privacy Policy – About Information we collect and how we use it » Komparify Blog » Komparify helps you find the best plan!

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or use our service.

## Your Personal Information

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address, mobile phone number and for some services address etc.

## Your Mobile Usage Pattern

Komparify.com may collect your current or estimated mobile usage pattern entered on our website by you to access our service. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. If you decide to create an account on our system, we store that usage pattern on our servers and use that for services like the ones detailed below.

## Your Searches and Search Results

Komparify.com also stores your searches, search results and estimated monthly cost.

## Your Mobile Call Log, SMS Log & Data Log

Komparify.com may collect information on the calls you make from your mobile phone and analyse the call and sms log to get your usage pattern.

## Your Third Party Authentication Information

Komparify.com may collect third party authentication information if you decide to use these services to authenticate with us. We also collect email addresses if you give us permission to import your contacts.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

## To improve our website

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

## To send periodic emails and SMS’

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. We may also send you emails to tell you about customized offers and or newer offerings which may help you save money. We may also send you emails to apprise you of problems with our systems which negatively impacted you.

## Market Research Participation

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## Aggregated Research

We use aggregated information on searches for intelligence on the mobile market and usage patterns. We use this information for understanding customers and the market and for special schemes and other such services.

## Advertising

We use information that we collect to target advertisements and to apprise you of special offers from select third parties.

## Selling Services

If you indicate that you would like to purchase services from us or a third party, We will share your contact information and other relevant details in order to help the third party to complete the transaction.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit or access your personal information. However we are not legally responsible for the accidental leakage of this information.

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe that such release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect others or ours rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Children’s Privacy

We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old and above.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date.

## Disclaimer for Links from Kompairfy.com

Komparify.com contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We do not monitor or control the content of such linked sites. Those sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we recommend you to review if you visit any linked web sites.

## Disclaimer for Links to Komparify.com

We are not responsible for the content of links to Komparify.com and their accuracy. We welcome links to Komparify.com from external sites but are in no way responsible for their accuracy. Links on this website may also change without prior notice.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by:

e-mail: komparify@cheenilabs.com

writing to :

Cheeni Labs, 3-H Century Plaza, 560 Anna Salai, Teynampet, Chennai 18
